<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<results>
<result>
<title>"New Cars, Used Cars, Car Dealers, Prices &amp; Reviews | Cars.com"</title>
<url>"https://www.cars.com/"</url>
<description>"Shop new &amp; used cars, research &amp; compare models, find local dealers/sellers, 
calculate payments, value your car, sell/trade in your car &amp; more at Cars.com."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"CALIFORNIA ASSOCIATION OF REALTORS® - www.car.org"</title>
<url>"https://www.car.org/"</url>
<description>"A real estate trade association to develop and promote programs/services that 
enhance a member's ability to conduct business with integrity and competency."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Used Cars for Sale - CarMax"</title>
<url>"https://www.carmax.com/cars"</url>
<description>"Search for new and used cars at carmax.com. Use our car search or research 
makes and models with customer reviews, expert reviews, and more."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"New Cars for Sale - Autotrader"</title>
<url>"https://www.autotrader.com/new-cars"</url>
<description>"Buying a new car can be a big moment in a driver's life. It might be the biggest 
purchase you ever make other than a home so it pays to do some research into ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"New Cars For Sale. Find new cars in your area. - CarGurus"</title>
<url>"https://www.cargurus.com/Cars/new/"</url>
<description>"Search new car listings to find the best local deals. We analyze millions of used 
cars daily."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Car and Driver: New Car Reviews, Buying Advice and News"</title>
<url>"https://www.caranddriver.com/"</url>
<description>"Covering the automotive industry since 1955 with in-depth reviews and analysis, 
features, auto show reporting, and advice for car owners and buyers."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Car - Wikipedia"</title>
<url>"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Car"</url>
<description>"A car (or automobile) is a wheeled motor vehicle used for transportation. Most 
definitions of car say they run primarily on roads, seat one to eight people, have ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"New cars, car reviews and pricing - Roadshow by CNET"</title>
<url>"https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/"</url>
<description>"Find and research the best new cars, get best pricing on your next vehicle, and 
stay up to date with industry news, auto shows and more from Roadshow by ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"What Car? - YouTube"</title>
<url>"https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC-GJbheknHZhSM7-Jgn63jg"</url>
<description>"What Car? is the UK's biggest car-buying brand and has been helping Britain's 
car buyers make purchasing decisions for over 40 years. Our tests are widely re..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Car Talk"</title>
<url>"https://www.cartalk.com/"</url>
<description>"Online Drivers Ed - Get your license, save on insurance, fix a ticket · How to 
Jumpstart a Car - Without exploding yourself into the next zip code · Selling Your 
Car ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"New Cars &amp; New Car Prices | Kelley Blue Book"</title>
<url>"https://www.kbb.com/new-cars/"</url>
<description>"Shop for new cars and new car prices at Kelley Blue Book's KBB.com. Search 
and compare hundreds of new car vehicle categories and models."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Opinion | Chuck Schumer: A Bold Plan for Clean Cars - The New ..."</title>
<url>"https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/24/opinion/chuck-schumer-electric-car.html"</url>
<description>"18 hours ago ... I have a proposal that is supported not just by environmentalists but also by labor 
and large automakers."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Used Cars for Sale | with Free CARFAX"</title>
<url>"https://www.carfax.com/cars-for-sale"</url>
<description>"A FREE CARFAX report comes with every used car and truck for sale on Carfax.
com. Start your search for 1-owner and accident-free cars to get a great deal."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Electric car prices finally in reach of millennial, Gen Z buyers"</title>
<url>"https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/20/electric-car-prices-finally-in-reach-of-millennial-gen-z-buyers.html"</url>
<description>"The cost gap between electric cars like the Nissan Leaf and traditional cars like 
the Nissan Maxima is shrinking, making the car-buying decision easier for a ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Be Car Care Aware | CarCare.org"</title>
<url>"http://www.carcare.org/"</url>
<description>"The Car Care Council is a non-profit organization dedicated to educating 
motorists about the importance of regular vehicle care, maintenance and repair ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"A kayaker rescued a woman trapped in a submerged car for hours ..."</title>
<url>"https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/24/us/car-submerged-rescue-trnd/index.html"</url>
<description>"17 hours ago ... A kayaker in Florida is being hailed as a hero by police after he rescued an 81-
year-old woman who was trapped inside her submerged car for ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Nissan's new electric concept car looks like a solid successor to the ..."</title>
<url>"https://www.theverge.com/2019/10/24/20930228/nissan-ariya-electric-concept-suv-tokyo-motor-show-2019"</url>
<description>"22 hours ago ... Nissan unveiled a new electric concept car this week at the 2019 Tokyo Motor 
Show called the Ariya. Instead of including strange gimmicks like ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Scientists have trained rats to drive tiny cars to collect food | New ..."</title>
<url>"https://www.newscientist.com/article/2220721-scientists-have-trained-rats-to-drive-tiny-cars-to-collect-food/"</url>
<description>"3 days ago ... Rats have mastered the art of driving a tiny car, suggesting that their brains are 
more flexible than we thought. The finding could be used to ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"Electric car start-ups — once seen as threat — now struggle to survive"</title>
<url>"https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/19/electric-car-start-ups-once-seen-as-threat-now-struggle-to-survive.html"</url>
<description>"6 days ago ... The move could complicate the already perilous situation for the electric car start-
up Jia helped launch, Faraday Future. Itself laden with debt ..."</description>
</result>
<result>
<title>"If You Got A 7-Year (Or Longer) Car Loan, We Want To Hear From ..."</title>
<url>"https://www.npr.org/2019/10/24/772363718/if-you-got-a-7-year-or-longer-car-loan-we-want-to-hear-from-you"</url>
<description>"20 hours ago ... More car buyers are taking out longer-term loans. And many are rolling over 
unpaid debt from their last car into their new loans. If you're ..."</description>
</result>
</results>
